geekscape.net 2014-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Geekscape

First and foremost, we are not going to sell your information to any lists. Signing up for Geekscape.net will not make you a part of any SPAM lists and it will not put you on any mailing lists that are not associated with Geekscape.net.

This Privacy Policy helps us make sure that we’re creating a community representative of YOU and the things that YOU care about. The below guidelines are to help you understand the information we collect, where it goes and how we can keep Gilmore from using it for his own purposes. We do our job to protect it… and Super Action Man has our backs in case we get compromised.

###  **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may also visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to our site and other sites.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

###  **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

 **To personalize your experience:** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

 **To improve our website:** (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you and your preferences)

 **To improve customer service:** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

 **To process transactions:** Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

 **Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email that should not take you long to get through at all.

###  **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server for your ID, profile information and passwords. No one affiliated with Geekscape will ever ask you for sensitive/credit information. If you are ever asked to provide this information, you are purchasing an item off site through one of our trusted partners.

Our shirts, ads and other merchandise are all handle through third party partners that are linked from the site. We are not able to access any of this protected information or will we ever attempt to access it. We’ve looked long and hard to find partners that will handle you credit information securely.

###  **Do we use cookies?**

Yes we do, but so does everyone else. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it, your default settings should be “on”) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are only permitted to use the information collected on our behalf to help us conduct and improve our business.

###  **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

###  **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

###  **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

###  **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###  **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

###  **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.geekscape.net/terms_of_service](http://geekscape.net/terms_of_service).

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

See all Features ->

### **PODCASTS**

  * The 2nd of 3 Live Podcast Episodes from TanoshiiCon

[ Read More](http://www.geekscape.net/the-saint-mort-show-episode-75-starting-a-writers-group-live-panel-from-tanoshiicon "The Saint Mort Show Episode 75: Starting a Writer’s Group \(Live Panel from TanoshiiCon\)")

Published on March 25, 2014

  * Also, what are the differences in all the cons going into Con Season?

  * Ardmore Junction is the compelling story of a homeless man who affected 6 people. Writer/Director Brian Gallagher came on the Saint Mort Show podcast to promote the film and it’s kickstarter.

[ Read More](http://www.geekscape.net/the-saint-mort-show-episode-074-brian-gallagher-writerdirector-of-ardmore-junction "The Saint Mort Show Episode 074: Brian Gallagher \(writer/director of Ardmore Junction\)")

  * In the first of three panels from TanoshiiCon Mort sat down with Steph and Tim from Episode 59 to talk about making a movie on a budget.

### **Community Discussion**
